Finding Aid for the Ralph J. Bunche papers LSC.2051
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1927-1971; 173 boxes
  - Ste-Su, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Sw-Sy, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - T, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Un, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Ur, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - V, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Wa-Wh, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Wh-Wi, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Wo-Wy, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Y, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Z, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Hate mail, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Social invitations (1 of 5), 1954 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Social invitations (2 of 5), 1954 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Social invitations (3 of 5), 1954 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (4 of 5), 1954 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Social invitations (5 of 5), 1954 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Ab-Am, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Am, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - An-Az, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Ba-Be, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Bi-Bo, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Br-By, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Ca, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Ca-Ch, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Ci-Co, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Co-Cu, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Da-De, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Dh-Du, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - E, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Fa-Fo, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Fo-Fu, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Ga-Go, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Gr-Gu, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Ha-Hi, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Ho-Hu, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - I, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - J, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Ka, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Ke-Ky, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - La-Le, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Li-Ly, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Ma-Mem, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Men-Mou, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Mow-Mu, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Na, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Na-Nu, 1955 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - O, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Pa-Po, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Po-Pu, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Ra-Ri, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Ro-Ru, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Sc, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Se-So, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - So-Sy, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - T, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - U, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - V, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Wa-Wh, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Wi-We, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Wr-Wy, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Y, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Z, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Hate mail, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Social invitations (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Social invitations (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Social invitations (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Aa-Am, 1956 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Am-An, 1956 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Ap-Ay, 1956 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Ba, 1956 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Be-Bl, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Bn-Br, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Bu, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Ca, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Ca-Ch, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Ch-Com, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Con-Cu, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Da-Der, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Des-Du, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - E, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Fa-Fo, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Fo-Fu, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - G, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Ha-He, 1956 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Hi-Hy, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - I, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - J, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Ka, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Ke-Ku, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Telegram, 1956 February 22, to Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr.
  - La-Le, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Li-Ly, 1956 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Me, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Me-Moo, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Mor-My, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Na, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Nd-Ne, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Ni-No, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - O, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Pa-Pi, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Pl-Pu, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Q, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Ra, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Re-Ro, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Ro-Ry, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Sa-Se, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Sh-Sig, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Sil-So, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Sp-St, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Su-Sy, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Ta-Ti, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - To-Tw, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Un, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Un-Ut, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - V, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Wa-Wen, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Web-Wil, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Win-Wo, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Wo-Wy, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - X, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Z, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Hate mail, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Social Invitations (1 of 3), 1956 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Social Invitations (2 of 3), 1956 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Social Invitations (3 of 3), 1956 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Ab-Am, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Am-Aug, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Aug-Av, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Ba-Be, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Bi-Br, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Bu, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Ca-Ch, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Ch-Ci, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Cl-Cu, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Da-Dr, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Du, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - E, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Fa-Fl, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Fo-Fu, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Ga-Gl, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Letter, 1957 February 7, New York, N.Y. to Mr. John Gatling, Philadelphia, Pa
  - Go-Gu, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Ha-He, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Hi-Hu, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - I, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - J, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - K, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Telegram, 1957 January 8, Atlanta, Ga. to Ralph J. Bunche, New York, N.Y.
    - Telegram, 1957 January 8, New York, N.Y. to the Reverends Martin Luther King, G. K. Steele and Erle Shuttlesworth, Atlanta, Ga
      Typescript transcript of telegram (night letter)
  - L, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Mc, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Me-Mo, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Mo-My, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Na, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Ne-Ny, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - O, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Pa-Po, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Pr-Pu, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Q, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Ri, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Ro-Ru, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Sa-Se, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Sh-Sn, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - So-Sw, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - T, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - U, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - V, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Wa-Wil, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Win-Wu, 1957 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - X-Y, 1957 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Z, 1957 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Hate mail (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Hate mail (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Social invitations (1 of 5), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Social invitations (2 of 5), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Social invitations (3 of 5), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Social invitations (4 of 5), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (5 of 5), 1957 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Ab-Am, 1958 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Am-Asc, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Asi-Au, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Ba-Bi, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Bl-Br, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Br-Bu, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Ca-Cha, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Che-Com, 1958 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Con-Cu, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Da-Di, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Do-Du, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - E, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - F, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - G, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Ha-He, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Hi-Hu, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - I, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Letter, 1959 May 28, to Dr. Cecilia Irvine, Los Angeles, California
      Letter to Dr. Irvine, Bunche's former teacher at Jefferson High School in Los Angeles, on the occasion of her retirement from the University of California, Los Angeles.
    - Letter, 1959 June 10, University of California, Los Angeles, to Dr. Ralph R. [sic] Bunche, United Nations, New York City
  - J, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Ka-Ke, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Ki-Kw, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - La-Lin, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Lio-Ly, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Me, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Me-Mo, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Mo-My, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Na, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Ne, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Ni-Ny, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - O, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Pa-Pe, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Pe-Pu, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Q, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Ra-Ri, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Ro-Ru, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Sa-Sh, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sto, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Str-Sy, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - T, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - U, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - V, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Wa-Wh, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Wi-Wo, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Wr-Wu, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - X-Y, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Z, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Hate mail, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (1 of 6), 1958 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Social invitations (2 of 6), 1958 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Social invitations (3 of 6), 1958 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Social invitations (4 of 6), 1958 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Social invitations (5 of 6), 1958 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Social invitations (6 of 6), 1958 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Aa-Af, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Ag-Am, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Am-An, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Ap-Au, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Ba-Bi, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Bl-Bo, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Br, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Bu, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Ca, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Ce-Ch, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Ch-Col, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Col-Coo, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Cor-Cu, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Da-Doo, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Dor-Dy, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Ea-Ele, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Eli-Ex, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Fa-Fl, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Fo-Fu, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Ga-Gor, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Gos-Gu, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Ha-Hay, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Haz-He, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Hi-Hof, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Hol-Hy, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - I, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Ja-Joh, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Joi-Ju, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Ka-Kh, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Ki-Kw, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - La-Lex, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Lew-Ly, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Ma-Mc, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Me-Mi, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Mo, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Mu-My, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Na, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Na-Ne, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Ne-Ny, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - O, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Pa, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Letter, 1964 May 5, Nicosia, Cyprus, to Mr. Ralph Bunche, United Nations Under-Secretary for Political Affairs, New York, N.Y.
      At head of page: Minister of Communication and Works.
  - Pe-Pin, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Pir-Pu, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Q, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Red, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Reg-Ros, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Rot-Ry, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Scho, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Schr-Si, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Sk-Sto, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - St-Sw, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - T, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Ud-Un, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Ur-Us, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - V, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Wa-We, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - We-Win, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Wis-Wo, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Wr-Wy, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Y, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Z, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Hate mail (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Hate mail (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Social invitations (1 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Social invitations (2 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Social invitations (3 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Social invitations (4 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (5 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Social invitations (6 of 6), 1959 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Ab-Am, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Am, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - An-As, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - At-Au, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Ba-Ben, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Ber-Bon, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Bor-Bro, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Bro-Bus, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - But-By, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Letter, 1960 March 9, Washington D.C., to Ralph J. Bunche, New York, N.Y.
      handwritten letter
    - Letter, 1960 March 10, New York, N.Y. to Mr. Marcellus Butler, Washington, D.C.
  - Cal-Car, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Cas-Ch, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Ci-Co, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Co, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Cow-Cu, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Da, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - De-Do, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Dr-Du, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Ea-En, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Ep-Ey, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Fa-For, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Fou-Fu, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Ga-Gil, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Gir-Gu, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Ha, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - He-Ho, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Ho-Hu, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Hu, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - I, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - J, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Ka, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Ke-Ko, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Kp-Ky, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - La-Lea, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Leb-Ly, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Ma-Mc, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Mc-Mi, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Moc-Mos, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Mou-Mw, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Na, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Na-Ne, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Ne-Ny, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - O, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Pa, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Pe-Ph, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Pi-Pr, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Pu, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Q, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Red, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Ref-Ri, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Ro-Ry, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sca, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Sch-Sh, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Si-Sn, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - So-Sr, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - St-Sy, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Ta-Thi, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Tho-Ty, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Un, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Up-Ut, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - V, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Wa-We, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - We-Wi, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Wo-Wy, 1960 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - X-Y, 1960 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Z, 1960 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Congo mission, A-F, 1960 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    This folder contains a photocopy of a letter sent from the Stanley Palace Hotel, Avenue Moulaert, Leopoldville. Bunche writes of the revolt and his concerns about the Congo and expresses his love for his family.
    Existence and Location of Originals
    The original copy of this letter is housed within box 497 and stored in the safe at YRL Library Special Collections.
    - Letter, 1960 July 8, Leopoldville, Congo to Ralph Bunche, Jr.
      Photocopy of letter sent from the Stanley Palace Hotel, Avenue Moulaert, Leopoldville. Bunche writes of the revolt and his concerns about the Congo and expresses his love for his family.
  - Congo mission, G-M, 1960 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Congo mission, N-Z, 1960 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Hate mail (1 of 3), 1960 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Hate mail (2 of 3), 1960 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Hate mail (3 of 3), 1960 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (1 of 3), 1960 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - Social invitations (2 of 3), 1960 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Social invitations (3 of 3), 1960 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Ab-Al, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Am-An, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Ar-Au, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Ba-Bet, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Bev-Bri, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Bro-By, 1961 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Ca-Ce, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Ch-Cl, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Co, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Co-Cu, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Da, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Da-De, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Di-Du, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - E, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Fa-Fl, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Fo-Fu, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Ga-Gl, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Gl, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Gl-Go, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Gr-Gu, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Ha-Hen, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Her-Ho, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Hu, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - I, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Ja-Je, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Jo-Ju, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Ka-Kil, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Kin-Kh, 1961 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - La-Le, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Li-Ly, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Ma, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Mc-Mil, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Min-Mo, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Mo-Mz, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Na-Nel, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - New, 1961 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Nh-Ny, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - O, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Pa-Pea, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Pei-Po, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Pr-Py, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Q, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Ra-Ren, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Res-Reu, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - Ro, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Ru-Ry, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sch, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Sci-Sm, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Sn-Str, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Stu-Sy, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Ta-Ti, 1961 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - To-Tu, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Un, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Un-Uz, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - V, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Wa-We, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - We-Wol, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Wom-Wu, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - X-Y, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Z, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - UN Operation in Congo, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Hate mail (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Hate mail (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Hate mail (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Social invitations (1 of 4), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Social invitations (2 of 4), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Social invitations (3 of 4), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Social invitations (4 of 4), 1961 (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - Aa-Ala, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Alb-Am, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Am-An, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - An-Ax, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Ba, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Be-Bl, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Bl-Br, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Br, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Bu-By, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Ca, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Ce-Ch, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Ci-Coll, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Colo-Cou, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Cow-Cu, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Da, 1962 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Da-Del, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Dem-Dut, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Duv-Dy, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Ea-Em, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - En-Ez, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Fa-Fol, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Fon-Fr, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Fr-Fu, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Ga, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Ge-Gl, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Go-Gri, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Gro-Gu, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Haa-Har, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Has-Hi, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Ho, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Hu, 1962 (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Il-In, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Ir-Iv, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Ja-Joh, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Joi-Ju, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Ka-Kin, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Kis-Ky, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - La-Leo, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Let-Ly, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Ma (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Ma (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Mb-Me, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Mi, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Moh-Mos, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Mou-My, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Na, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Na-Ne, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Ne-No, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - No-Nu, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Ob-Or, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Ow-Ox, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Pa-Pel, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Pen-Pl, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Po-Pu, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Q, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Ra-Reu, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Rey-Roc, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Roe-Roy, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Ru-Ry, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Sai-Sar, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Sas-Sch, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Sch-Sil, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Sim-Sp, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Sr-Sz, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Ta-Ti, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - To-Tu, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - U, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - V, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Wa, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - We-Wh, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Wi-Woo, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Wor-Wy, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - X-Y, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Z, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - UN Operation in Congo, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Hate mail (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Hate mail (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Hate mail (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Social invitations (1 of 5), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Social invitations (2 of 5), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Social invitations (3 of 5), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Social invitations (4 of 5), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Social invitations (5 of 5), 1962 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Ab-Ala, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Alb-Am, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Ame, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Ami-Asc, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Ash-Az, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Ba-Bec, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Bed-Bor, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Bos-Bro, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Bru-By, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Ca, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Ch, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Cl-Com, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Con-Cu, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Da-Dec, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Dee-Dh, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Di-Du, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Ea-Ep, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Eq-Ew, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Fa-Fle, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Fli-Fos, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Fou-Fu, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Ga-God, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Gol-Gu, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Had-Har, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Has-Hof, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Hog-Hy, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Ih-In, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - In-Is, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Ja-Jo, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Jo-Ju, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Ka, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Ke-Ki, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Letter, 1963 May 11, to the Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Birmingham, Alabama
  - Kj-Ku, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Ralph Bunche on civil rights: interview with Mr. Woody Klein, New York World-Telegram, 1963 July 29
    - Letter, 1963 July 29, New York, N.Y. to Mr. Woody Klein, New York, N.Y.
      Cover letter from Joan Klein, Ralph Bunche's secretary. Refers to Klein's notes (enclosed) on his interview with Bunche, which Bunche has edited.
  - La-Ler, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Les-Li, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Lo-Ly, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Ma, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Mc-Mil, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Min-Mor, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Mos-My, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Na-Net, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - New, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Ng-Nu, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - O, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Pa-Ph, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Pi-Pr, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Pu-Py, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Q, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Ra-Rei, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Res-Rob, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Rob, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 7)